hey everyone welcome back to our Channel
I am back with another interesting topic
in the Tosca Autumn we have been talking
about the execution list
so let's talk about how we can change
the view of the default execution lists
so when we are looking at an execution
list folder it displays a certain view
right so there are certain columns which
are displayed I can always add more
columns by going to column Chooser and
then add more columns to this particular
view or I can even remove some of the
columns right but apart from this you
can also change the default view which
means you can change the details which
are displayed on this particular View
and then you can add more details or
change the whole uh structure of how the
results are displayed on the execution
list
to do that you need to go to the view
Tab and Under The View tab you will find
the execution list
now if you click on the drop down you
will see there are few options which are
already selected okay and these are the
default options which are enabled when
you open an execution list
now there are few other options so let's
go through each of the option and let's
see what it does or how it changes the
view of the execution list
so if I enable this show only last
actual log you will see it will reduce
the number of actual logs it will only
show you the last actual log which means
the actual log which was generated after
you executed it and it is only for the
last time okay
then you can also enable multi-line logs
So currently you can see in the log info
it is only displaying a one liner right
for your executions either it is past or
field
now if I enable this multi-line logs you
will see it will show more details here
in a multi-line format okay and this
could be useful to debug your execution
failures
then the show statistics only on visible
execution lists right so the stats will
only be shown for the visible execution
list now if I disable this you will see
a lot of stats are gone from the view
right
so let's keep it enabled also this show
statistics logarithmically
previously you could see these were
extended for the whole uh column but now
you can see these are reduced okay
then uh show statistics if I disable
this you will see all the details are
suppressed right so no bars are
displayed and it doesn't tell you
whether the test case has passed and how
much it has passed how much it has
failed right
so you can always enable this show
statistics and it will show you these
details here
then you can also enable the show failed
logs only okay
so here you will see that it will show
the logs for your failed test cases
and then if you want to change the
format of this duration currently it is
displaying it in a hour and minute and
seconds format right we can change it to
show only in duration of seconds
so here you will see the duration is now
being shown in seconds okay
so that could be useful uh for tracking
how much time it took to execute a
particular step or test case
so as you can see there are lots of
different options available uh in the
view tab for execution list and you can
take uh advantage of that to change the
view of your execution list a little bit
to maybe include more details or to
exclude details which are not required
that's all for this particular video if
you have any questions then please leave
it in the comments
if you like this video then please
subscribe to our Channel
thanks for watching and I will see you
in the next video